[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "You're a kind of fiery, emotional, soulful character, aren't you -- on and often stage?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "kind", "of", "fiery", ",", "emotional", ",", "soulful", "character", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "--", "on", "and", "often", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "I'm just trying to live this interesting life we all have in front of us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "trying", "to", "live", "this", "interesting", "life", "we", "all", "have", "in", "front", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "When you look at your extraordinary life professional and personal, how do you feel now about where you've arrived, where you are right now?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "your", "extraordinary", "life", "professional", "and", "personal", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "now", "about", "where", "you", "'ve", "arrived", ",", "where", "you", "are", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I think at this point, I'm 51 now, I've realized, oh, it's just a journey.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "at", "this", "point", ",", "I", "'m", "51", "now", ",", "I", "'ve", "realized", ",", "oh", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "a", "journey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "You're never actually going to arrive, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "never", "actually", "going", "to", "arrive", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What's been the moment if I could replay it for you, you'd relive?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "moment", "if", "I", "could", "replay", "it", "for", "you", ",", "you", "'d", "relive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Ooh.", "answer_tokens": ["Ooh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994"], "ORGANIZATION": ["MTV"]}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "CD", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "When was that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "That was 1994 unplugged, MTV.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "1994", "unplugged", ",", "MTV", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Was it as good as you always hoped?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "as", "good", "as", "you", "always", "hoped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes, looking back on it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "looking", "back", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "That's the kind of music you want to get your little Chevy, get on the, you know, I don't know the Pacific Coast highway, get the shades on, ramp up the Etheridge, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "kind", "of", "music", "you", "want", "to", "get", "your", "little", "Chevy", ",", "get", "on", "the", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "Pacific", "Coast", "highway", ",", "get", "the", "shades", "on", ",", "ramp", "up", "the", "Etheridge", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chevy"], "LOCATION": ["Pacific Coast"], "PERSON": ["Etheridge"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["Properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "So, before you felt that you'd been in love, but you haven't been able to give that person the whole you?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "before", "you", "felt", "that", "you", "'d", "been", "in", "love", ",", "but", "you", "have", "n't", "been", "able", "to", "give", "that", "person", "the", "whole", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, I -- myself was, I felt owed; they'll fill this up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "myself", "was", ",", "I", "felt", "owed", ";", "they", "'ll", "fill", "this", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Have I cracked the Holy Grail of love?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "I", "cracked", "the", "Holy", "Grail", "of", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Terribly cheesy phrase, I know.", "answer_tokens": ["Terribly", "cheesy", "phrase", ",", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Because it's when you're the most searing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "when", "you", "'re", "the", "most", "searing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, it depends on how you look at it .", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "depends", "on", "how", "you", "look", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Can you write good stuff if you're really happy?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "write", "good", "stuff", "if", "you", "'re", "really", "happy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Can you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "-- from the artistry of your songwriting, if I said, write, you can be in this kind of existential state of pure bliss for the next 30 years, or torment, which would produce the better music, the better songs?", "question_tokens": ["--", "from", "the", "artistry", "of", "your", "songwriting", ",", "if", "I", "said", ",", "write", ",", "you", "can", "be", "in", "this", "kind", "of", "existential", "state", "of", "pure", "bliss", "for", "the", "next", "30", "years", ",", "or", "torment", ",", "which", "would", "produce", "the", "better", "music", ",", "the", "better", "songs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "See, as you ask me that, this state of bliss you're talking about cannot exist without the other side, without the darker side.", "answer_tokens": ["See", ",", "as", "you", "ask", "me", "that", ",", "this", "state", "of", "bliss", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "can", "not", "exist", "without", "the", "other", "side", ",", "without", "the", "darker", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "What would produce the better songs?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "produce", "the", "better", "songs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "The contrast of misery, of course, is going to -- the contrast, that -- it's the desire to be out of that, into the bliss.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "contrast", "of", "misery", ",", "of", "course", ",", "is", "going", "to", "--", "the", "contrast", ",", "that", "--", "it", "'s", "the", "desire", "to", "be", "out", "of", "that", ",", "into", "the", "bliss", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Or are you still thinking, you know what, a lot of talk, not enough action?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "still", "thinking", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "talk", ",", "not", "enough", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Having been on the journey of getting towards gay and lesbian rights, equality, understanding, diversity in America, 20 years ago, started the, you know, no, I was hoping in 10 years it would all be -- we'd all feel comfortable about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Having", "been", "on", "the", "journey", "of", "getting", "towards", "gay", "and", "lesbian", "rights", ",", "equality", ",", "understanding", ",", "diversity", "in", "America", ",", "20", "years", "ago", ",", "started", "the", ",", "you", "know", ",", "no", ",", "I", "was", "hoping", "in", "10", "years", "it", "would", "all", "be", "--", "we", "'d", "all", "feel", "comfortable", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "But do you feel that the them that is you and those who are, again, lesbian like you, are in a much better position now that you have a president prepared to go on television and say, \"I support\"?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "the", "them", "that", "is", "you", "and", "those", "who", "are", ",", "again", ",", "lesbian", "like", "you", ",", "are", "in", "a", "much", "better", "position", "now", "that", "you", "have", "a", "president", "prepared", "to", "go", "on", "television", "and", "say", ",", "``", "I", "support", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "WP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Is there more tolerance?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "more", "tolerance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Tolerance, you know, I don't even like to use the word tolerance.", "answer_tokens": ["Tolerance", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "like", "to", "use", "the", "word", "tolerance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What's the right word?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "right", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Because it sounds like, you know, I'm doing something that you have to tolerate.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "sounds", "like", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "doing", "something", "that", "you", "have", "to", "tolerate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'60s"], "LOCATION": ["Kansas"]}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "But you feel it's getting better, even in states like Kansas?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "feel", "it", "'s", "getting", "better", ",", "even", "in", "states", "like", "Kansas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Especially Kansas, because I came from the Kansas in the '60s, which was the middle of the civil rights movement.", "answer_tokens": ["Especially", "Kansas", ",", "because", "I", "came", "from", "the", "Kansas", "in", "the", "'60s", ",", "which", "was", "the", "middle", "of", "the", "civil", "rights", "movement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kansas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "And what do you think is the potential prospect of a Mitt Romney presidency?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "potential", "prospect", "of", "a", "Mitt", "Romney", "presidency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "What -- is that linked to what you said to me, that basically you've learned to love yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "is", "that", "linked", "to", "what", "you", "said", "to", "me", ",", "that", "basically", "you", "'ve", "learned", "to", "love", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "But do you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Yes, you can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "What is the longest period you've ever had, where you literally couldn't write a song, of any quality at all?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "longest", "period", "you", "'ve", "ever", "had", ",", "where", "you", "literally", "could", "n't", "write", "a", "song", ",", "of", "any", "quality", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Wow, well, I started writing when I was 10.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "well", ",", "I", "started", "writing", "when", "I", "was", "10", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Do you get long blank periods, though?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "long", "blank", "periods", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Why did you feel that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "feel", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I was being a good grownup.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "being", "a", "good", "grownup", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "If, God forbid, you were struck again by cancer, it came back or whatever, would you take marijuana?", "question_tokens": ["If", ",", "God", "forbid", ",", "you", "were", "struck", "again", "by", "cancer", ",", "it", "came", "back", "or", "whatever", ",", "would", "you", "take", "marijuana", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What do you want to be in five years' time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "to", "be", "in", "five", "years", "'", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I want to still be creating.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "still", "be", "creating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "You must be proud of them, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "proud", "of", "them", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I actually haven't seen that for a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "have", "n't", "seen", "that", "for", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Difficult to film I should think, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Difficult", "to", "film", "I", "should", "think", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Oh that scene was easy.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "that", "scene", "was", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "To eternity vitality?", "question_tokens": ["To", "eternity", "vitality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Lots of virgin blood.", "answer_tokens": ["Lots", "of", "virgin", "blood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Why is that extraordinary?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "extraordinary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "It just seems such a tragic waste for somebody.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "just", "seems", "such", "a", "tragic", "waste", "for", "somebody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "How's it going?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "it", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "ever", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Do you dream of a fairy tale white wedding one day?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "dream", "of", "a", "fairy", "tale", "white", "wedding", "one", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "No, I never have.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "That would be really difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "really", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "You are with somebody at the moment, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "with", "somebody", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I am, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "How's that going?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "that", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "It's going great.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "How many times would you say you have been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "would", "you", "say", "you", "have", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Define properly.", "answer_tokens": ["Define", "properly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Do you like being the object of male attention in that way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "being", "the", "object", "of", "male", "attention", "in", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Well, it's better than looking and saying, she looks like (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "better", "than", "looking", "and", "saying", ",", "she", "looks", "like", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What am I supposed to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "am", "I", "supposed", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Tell her the story.", "answer_tokens": ["Tell", "her", "the", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What story?", "question_tokens": ["What", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "The situation.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "I'm riding her over to the thrifty, ain't I?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "riding", "her", "over", "to", "the", "thrifty", ",", "ai", "n't", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Is he as nice to work with as I imagine he is?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "as", "nice", "to", "work", "with", "as", "I", "imagine", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "He -- first of all, he's so fantastic in this movie.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "'s", "so", "fantastic", "in", "this", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Did she ever respond?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "ever", "respond", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "You never met her?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "met", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "No, sadly.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "sadly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Do you take much of an interesting in it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "take", "much", "of", "an", "interesting", "in", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "You know, probably not as much as I should.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "probably", "not", "as", "much", "as", "I", "should", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ":", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Would you again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "At this -- if -- at this very moment, I would.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "this", "--", "if", "--", "at", "this", "very", "moment", ",", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", ":", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Just because I feel like I should be more -- a little bit more informed at this moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "because", "I", "feel", "like", "I", "should", "be", "more", "--", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "informed", "at", "this", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "What's the one thing you'd change for America to make it better?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "one", "thing", "you", "'d", "change", "for", "America", "to", "make", "it", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "I would try to simplify everything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "try", "to", "simplify", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "How did this happen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "this", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Well, I believe I have a gift of shooting archery.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "I", "have", "a", "gift", "of", "shooting", "archery", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "You have only been doing this for two or three years properly?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "only", "been", "doing", "this", "for", "two", "or", "three", "years", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Where do you get that from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "It is instilled in me from my parents.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "instilled", "in", "me", "from", "my", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "What are does it mean to be representing America in the Paralympic Games?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "be", "representing", "America", "in", "the", "Paralympic", "Games", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I'm just smiling, because it's such an honor and a privilege to be able to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "smiling", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "such", "an", "honor", "and", "a", "privilege", "to", "be", "able", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "That's the plan.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "plan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "You don't like coming in second, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "like", "coming", "in", "second", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carter"]}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "What do they make of their dad?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "make", "of", "their", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "My oldest is Carter.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "oldest", "is", "Carter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120812pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "What is the lesson you learned?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "lesson", "you", "learned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Not to ever come back.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "to", "ever", "come", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]